

Casey Jenkins

Denver, CO 805-458-7859 caseyjenkins92@gmail.com www.caseyjenkins.dev linkedin.com/in/caseykins github.com/caseykins

I am a full-stack software developer that enjoys solving problems, creating systems, increasing efficiency, and working in front-end design. With years of experience in bio-tech and electrical work, I possess strong problem solving skills, acute attention to detail, and determination to get the job done well. I enjoy troubleshooting and seeing projects from start to finish, never settling to do less than my best. My goal is to create intuitive and relevant apps that enrich the users' experience and improve everyday living.

Technical Skills

JavaScript | HTML | CSS

React | Express | Python

Node.js | Sequelize | SQL

PostgreSQL | Sass | Git | EJS

Projects

CardBoard

Express | EJS | Node.js | PostgreSQL | Sequelize | CSS | JavaScript | HTML

A web application based off of Trello, allowing users to create and customize digital to-do lists. Users can create any number of lists and list items, adding and deleting tasks as they go.

Brewser

React | Express | Node.js | PostgreSQL | Sequelize | Sass | JavaScript | HTML

A web application inspired by Untappd. Brewser allows users to search breweries based on location, using the OpenBreweryDB API and allows users to create beer reviews via check-ins.

Leafy Ledger

Express | EJS | Node.js | PostgreSQL | Sequelize | CSS | JavaScript | HTML

A web application designed to allow the user to find and research plants using the Trefle.io API. Once the user finds their desired plant, they can save the plant in their favorites and track each plant's watering schedule.

Experience

Safety & Warehouse Manager

Elson Electric, Inc • Pleasant Hill, CA

November 2018 - May 2020

- Assigned and administered field safety lessons to meet OSHA standards
- Represented the company when meeting with OSHA and insurance reps
- Supplied worksites to ensure proper safety and PPE requirements were met
- Managed supply warehouse, shipping and receiving, and vendor relations
- Supervised and scheduled a team of three people
- Set up systems for incoming and outgoing materials, ensuring that they are delivered to their proper destinations on time
- Ordered electrical and safety supplies and coordinated deliveries and pickup

Material Handler

Bio-Rad Laboratories • Hercules, CA

August 2015 - November 2018

- Maintained, tracked, and transferred over \$26 million of raw materials
- Managed inventory and communicated with buyers, vendors, and QC to ensure material and transactional accuracy
- Worked within a productive team and performed training of new employees
- Managed projects, overseeing massive inventory overhaul and cataloguing new materials
- Assisted Quality Control, performing measurements to determine materials were up to specifications using CMMs, telecentric illumination machines, scales, and various hand tools

Facilities Manager

Grace Central Coast • San Luis Obispo, CA

May 2013 - April 2015

- Managed a small team by assigning tasks, scheduling hours, and hiring personnel
- Performed custodial tasks, repairs, event setups, landscaping, and special events
- Coordinated with the event director to organize scheduling and event needs
- Managed inventory, budgeting, invoices, custodial accounts and events

Education

General Assembly • Remote

December, 2020

An intensive, twelve-week, 450+ hour certificate program focused on product development fundamentals, object-oriented programming, frameworks, MVC, data modeling, and team collaboration strategies. Completed with a portfolio of individual and group projects.

Cuesta College • San Luis Obispo, CA

May, 2012

Associate of Arts - Liberal Arts: Arts & Humanities